webpackJsonp([65856866535745],{469:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function r(e){return e&&e.__esModule?e:{default:e}}function i(e,a){if(!(e instanceof a))throw new TypeError("Cannot call a class as a function")}function l(e,a){if(!e)throw new ReferenceError("this hasn't been initialised - super() hasn't been called");return!a||"object"!=typeof a&&"function"!=typeof a?e:a}function o(e,a){if("function"!=typeof a&&null!==a)throw new TypeError("Super expression must either be null or a function, not "+typeof a);e.prototype=Object.create(a&&a.prototype,{constructor:{value:e,enumerable:!1,writable:!0,configurable:!0}}),a&&(Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf(e,a):e.__proto__=a)}a.__esModule=!0;var n=t(1),c=r(n),s=t(33),d=r(s),u=t(37);r(u);t(71);var m=t(49),f=r(m),p=[{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"1Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-1",href:"#collapse-1",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"2Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-2",href:"#collapse-2",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"3Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-3",href:"#collapse-3",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"4Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-4",href:"#collapse-4",display:!0},{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"5Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-5",href:"#collapse-5",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"6Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-6",href:"#collapse-6",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"7Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-7",href:"#collapse-7",display:!0}],h=[{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-1",href:"#collapse-tab2-1",display:!0},{question:"Who owns Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-2",href:"#collapse-tab2-2",display:!0},{question:"Why am I having trouble logging in?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-3",href:"#collapse-tab2-3",display:!0},{question:"How can I contact Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-4",href:"#collapse-tab2-4",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-5",href:"#collapse-tab2-5",display:!0},{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-6",href:"#collapse-tab2-6",display:!0}],b=(p.reverse(),h.reverse(),function(e){return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"card"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"card-header panel-heading",role:"tab",id:"headingOne"},c.default.createElement("a",{role:"button",className:"collapsed text-black","data-toggle":"collapse","data-parent":"#accordion","data-core":"",href:e.href,"aria-expanded":"false","aria-controls":"collapse1"},c.default.createElement("p",{className:"lead black display-5 mr-3"},c.default.createElement("span",{className:"sign mbr-iconfont mbri-arrow-down inactive"})," ",e.question))),c.default.createElement("div",{id:e.id,className:"panel-collapse noScroll collapse",role:"tabpanel","aria-labelledby":"headingOne"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"panel-body p-4"},c.default.createElement("p",{className:"mbr-fonts-style panel-text display-7"},e.answer))))}),y=p.map(b),w=y.slice(0,5),E=h.map(b),q=E.slice(0,5),g=function(e){function a(){return i(this,a),l(this,e.apply(this,arguments))}return o(a,e),a.prototype.render=function(){return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"pt-5 pb-1 mb-2",id:"content-14"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"features-banner","data-stellar-offset-parent":"true"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"f_vcenter"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"f_vbottom"},c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"profile-title display-4 font-weight-bold mb-2 "},"Questions")),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"f_rht pb-3"},c.default.createElement("nav",{"aria-label":"breadcrumb"},c.default.createElement("ol",{className:"breadcrumb"},c.default.createElement("li",{className:"breadcrumb-item"},c.default.createElement("a",{className:"breadcrumb-item ",href:"#"},"Home")),c.default.createElement("li",{className:"breadcrumb-item active","aria-current":"page"},"FaQ"))))))),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container pt-5 pb-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"f_rht ml-3 mr-3 mb-5 text-center"},c.default.createElement("h2",{className:"feat-title"},"Frequently Asked Questions"),c.default.createElement("span",{className:"lead black"},"Here are the most frequently asked questions at ZenForce. If you have a question not answered here - or throughout our webiste - please ",c.default.createElement(d.default,{className:"",to:"./contact"},"Contact Us"),".")),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"row pb-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"col-lg-8 col-md-10 col-sm-12 mx-auto"},c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2"},"Product"),c.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),w,c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2 mt-5"},"Sales"),c.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),q))),c.default.createElement(f.default,null))},a}(n.Component);a.default=g,e.exports=a.default}});
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-fa-q-js-4bf28b36a66adbdeddf6.js.map